Preliminary Inventory to the Fly Papers on Squatters' Rights TAM.363
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Fly Papers on Squatters' Rights
1980s-2000s
TAM.363
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
0.5 linear feet (1 box)
Fly.
Box 1
Historical/Biographical Note
Fly is a visual artist who was involved in the 1980s squatters' rights movement in New York City's East Village which culminated in the Tompkins Square Park Police Riot of August 1988.
Scope and Contents note
The collection consists of photographs, a scrapbook that contains clippings, artwork and photographs, and copies of zines, including Dog Days and Slug and Lettuce.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Fly sent a gift of his papers in 2006. The accession number associated with this gift is 2006.022.
Fly.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) |x Social conditions.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.).; Squatters |z New York (State) |z New York.; Tompkins Square Park Riot, New York, N.Y., 1988.
- Art Publications: Includes Dog Days and Peoples, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Artworks, Photos, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Clippings, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "Inside Out: The Art World of the Squats" Exhibition Catalogue, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Fliers, Leaflets, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Poster (framed), 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Posters, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Slug and Lettuce numbers 39--57, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Slug and Lettuce numbers 62--74, 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Slug and Lettuce numbers 79--85, 1990s-2000s; 0.5 linear feet (Box 1, Folder 10)